愿人類榮光永存
Glory to mankind
我們將重奪家園！
We will take back the seas,the skies,the land!
我們將從機器人手中奪回我們的世界
We will take back our world from the spurge of the machines
我們將戰無不勝 讓我們來終結這場該死的戰爭！
We will not fail in this mission. Here and now, we will put an end to this goddamn war!
地堡的后門已經被入侵.尤爾哈已經成為拋棄的棋子.
特別鳴謝
尼爾：機械紀元 2
時軸:白茶
發現一個不同個體.確認為敵人.
Found a different one. Recognized as an enemy.
糟糕！這些人已經被病毒感染了！
Damn! These people are infected with the virus！
翻譯：一葉障目
別過來!!
Stay away from me!!!!
可惡
It's too bad
校對&壓制:雪夜
死吧
Go away
弱爆了
You don't have a chance
接下來...
Next..
呸！
Spit!
我必須撤退了
I must retreat
我不能就這么一個人逃走
I won't escape without other
敵人越來越多了！2B！別管我快走！
There's more and more them. 2B. Leave me. Save yourself!
快跑！！
2B！Run！！
9S...
A2
你為什么不獨自逃走呢？
Why didn't you run away by yourself?
為什么這么問？
Why are you asking me that？
很久以前 有一個逃兵
A long time ago there was a deserter
她是唯一的幸存者
After his teammates died, and she was the only survivor
該死的！
Damn！
為什么不獨自逃走呢...
Why didn't you escape alone ？
放馬過來吧！
Bring it on!
太遲了！
Too late!
告訴我為什么！！！
Tell me why！！！
9S...
I'm leaving you this woman but 9S is mine
尤爾哈部隊肅清計劃
本字幕由夜桜字幕組制作
抓住她
Grab her
別走！不準你碰9S！
Come back！Don't touch 9S!
你這次跑步了了
You can not escape this
想搞點快樂的事情?
Wanna have a little fun together?
隨你們處置
Go ahead
那么你們下一步要做什么?
So, what are you guys gonna do first?
她的身體還有點價值
Her body is still worth something
只要別給玩死了就行
Do whatever you want. Just don't kill her.
住手!還給我!
stop!!!give it back!
看來你是不明白你現在的處境哈？
You don't seem to understand your situation
沒有黑匣子的2B不足為懼
We don't have to be afraid of you without your black box
可惡！
Damn！
這是真是難得的上等貨啊
It's been so long since I fucked girl
Rape her!!!Rape her!!!Rape her!!!Rape her!!!Rape her!!!
肏她！！！肏她！！！肏她！！！肏她！！！肏她！！！
2B好可愛的身體啊.2B妹妹
What a cute body! 2B
這妞可真美啊!!!
Wow she's so pretty!!!
2B 接下來我們可有很多快樂的事情要做哦
2B,we will do lots of nice things together
好軟啊!
Ohh!So soft!
糟糕!我動不了了!!
Shit!I can't get away!!!
居然穿這么暴露的衣服真是個色女人啊
Damn, your huge ass look really sexy in this revealing outfit.
你這是每天都在誘惑9S么???
Were you trying to seduce 9S everyday???
看你外表一直以為你是很強勢的女性
I thought that you were a strong wiled girl
這不是也能發出這么可愛的淫叫么?
She moans sound so cute
I.....I'm just scared....!Don't get cocky!!!
我...我只是嚇了一跳而已...!少給我得意忘形了!
你的白色內褲真的很撩人啊
White thong are so sexy
每天看著你裙下若隱若現的小內內
Every day watching the thong in your skirt flickering
接下來...
Next...
快瞧 快瞧!
Come on!Come on!
2B!你感覺的到我的手在如何的玩弄你吧?
2B!Can you feel that I'm touching directly?
閉嘴
Shut up
你是不是很享受啊???啊呀 你怎么臉紅了?
Hehe are you enjoying this??? Aren't you blushing?
別那么牛逼哄哄的!你這王八蛋!
Don't get cocky!!You bastard!
注意點你對我說話的態度.小姐
Mind how you address me, missy
No...
不要...
好大的奶啊
They're huge!!!
2B小妹妹 長著一對很棒的奶子呢!!!
2B little sister. Your tits are great!!
Don't stare me!!!
不要盯著我看!
現在你看起來像一個無助的小女孩
Now you actually look like a helpless little girl
不要盯著我看 9S!
Stop staring me 9s!!!
我才不會屈服呢!!!
I should't give up!!!
不....我不能屈服....他們正在調戲著我!
No.....I can't do this.....While he's teasing me!
我不敢相信,他這樣的調戲著我
I can't believe that his teasing
哇哦!這就是2B的小穴!
Uoooooh! This is 2B's pussy!!!
我找到了2B小姐姐的弱點了!
I found 2B's  g-spot !
你可以這樣直接高潮哦!
I'll make you cum!
我好恨啊!!!
I hate it!!!!....
我被綁著?
I'm tied up?
A2?
好了.你就在一邊乖乖的看著我們吧....
Well 2B, you can just watch how I'm doing it today....
They want to insult me in front of 9S.I knew I could not lose!
他們想在9S面前屈辱我.我絕對不能輸!
在你喜歡的人面前這樣屈辱的高潮吧
I'll make you squirt while your lover are watching
不要..
No！！
不要讓我在那個男人的面前...
Don't let me in front of that man
露出你騷貨的本性吧.在所有人的面前!
Expose bitch's ture color. In front of everyone!
別這樣欺負我!!!
Don't bully me like that!!
暴露了!!!我的弱點暴露了!!!
No!!!!He found it!!!!Agh!!!Uh!He found my weak spot!!!
You are making a scary face. But your pussy is so squishy and lewd.
擺著一副恐怖的表情.但小穴卻是黏糊糊的真色情啊
如果他用龜頭使勁的摩擦哪里的話....
If he grinds it......against that spot...
不要！停下！停下！停下！停下！停下！快停下！快停下啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊！
Stop!No!No!No!No!No!No!No!No!No!No!No!No!No!No!Nooooooooooooooo!
2B!!!!
Uaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!!!!!!!!!!
我要去了....
I'm cumming.....
A2你在做什么 ?
What are you doing? A2
哦...你干嘛那么害羞???
Oh...Why are you so shy???
在你做任務的時候
On your mission
你總是盯著2B的大圓屁股看吧?
Are you always secretly staring at 2B's big ass?
不要隨便偷看別人的記憶！
Don't look at other people's memory！
我不知道你為什么對E型機體(Executioner處刑者)產生了愛意.
I don't know how you would have a love for an executioner model.
我想你一定是寂寞到了一定程度.
I think you are lonely to a certain degree of it
你怎么知道地堡有后門的?
How do you know there's a back door in the bunker?
POD機給了我授權 在你昏迷的時候我駭客了你 并且看到了一些你的小秘密.
POD gave me permission. I hacked your memory. And see some little secrets.
多虧了你 我們拿到了尤爾哈的情報
Thanks to you. We got the whole Yorha project.
我們已經被尤爾哈的謊言蒙騙了那么久
We've been living under yorha's lies for so long
你不覺得是2B一直在欺騙你嗎？
Does it feel like 2B has been cheating on you?
閉嘴！
Shut up!
閉嘴啊！!！
Shut up!!!
我們都是一樣的
We are the same. You and I
我們都被拋棄了
We both were abandoned
我們都很孤獨
We all endure alone
你的雞雞已經硬邦邦得了
You've got erection here
當你負責維修2B的時候.居然在她昏迷狀態對她做了如此卑鄙的事情.
Why do you want to lock the door when you are working on repair 2B?
這段記憶都被你讀取出來了？
Do you even have to read this memory?
你喜歡2B 因為你太孤獨了
You love 2B because you're too lonely
夠了！我不想再聽你說的話了！
Stop it. I don't want to hear the word you saying!
真受不了啊!
I love it!
剛把你的小屄撐開 那股婊子騷就撲鼻而來
I just spread your pussy and I already smell the dirty scent of a bitch.
放開我！！！
Let me go!!!
And it's wet because you just came
小屄濕噠噠的.因為剛把你搞高潮了么?
我的雞吧已經硬的不行了
I'm rockhard already!
Stop it!! Let her go!!!
住手！放開她！！
我要插進去了!!!
I plunge it in!!!
放開她！！！
Let her go!!!
嘿嘿嘿 怎么樣2B?第一次嘗到雞吧的感覺很棒吧???
How does it feel??? do you like your first cock???
不要!!!
No!!!
嗷嗷啊嗷嗷~真是緊致!2B的小屄真是太棒了
It's so tight!2B.Your pussy is the best!
No!!!
不!!!
對不起 在中途停下來了....
Sorry for stopping in the middle like that....
Shit...!!Shit!!!!
該死的！該死啊！！
哦!還是第一次啊.血都流出來了!!!
Oooooh you're bleeding!Is this your frist time!!!???
真雞巴的爽啊!強奸這種強勢的女人實在很有征服感!!!
I love it feels good!!!I love raping strong girls!!!
剛剛已經知道你哪里最敏感了....
I know about your weak spot now....
喂!再給我享受點啊!
Come on!!!satisfy me some more!!!
我要殺了你們！！
I‘ ll kill all of you for this!
怎么樣 感覺舒服吧??
So..does that feel good???
我對這一點感覺都沒有!
I'm dead into all that!
哦 是么????
Oh..Is that so!?
我多么希望時光能回到從前...
Oh..How I wish time could go back towards...
趁著我現在還能保持清醒...
Before, I lose my mind...
讓我說
I want to tell you...
9S......對不起.....
9S, I am sorry...
我說謊了...對不起...可能你不會相信.....
I am sorry I lied to you...Maybe you won't believe me...
...夠了
...enough
夠了...
No..enough...
我是真的..喜歡9S你的啊
I really love you 9S
一次次的殺死你.....
I am killing you... over and over again...
消除你的記憶.....
Everytime I am wiping your memory...
而每次你都會重新愛上我.....
And everytime you love me again...
不知道從什么時候開始
I don't even remember when I started...
我也喜歡上了你
...to love you too
但是我無法違抗命令
But I couldn't disobey my orders
但現在我只想忠于自己的感情  和9S一起逃離這里...
But now I want to be true to my feeling and escape with you 9S
即使全世界拋棄了我們
Even if the whole world has no meaning
只要能和9S在一起
Your are my reason to live...
我也愿意獨自承受全世界的重量
I am willing to bear the weight of the world alone
和9S在一起的時候 真的好開心呢...
I am so happy when I am with you 9S...
2B..別再說了...
2B！！！Don't say anything more
和9S一起戰斗的時候....也很喜歡...
When we fight together...
和9S一起旅行的時候也....很喜歡....
When we travel together...
和9S一起玩的時候也是....
When we play together...
閉嘴!母狗！！！
Shut up!Bitch！！！
不要..
No！
該死的！該死啊！！
Shit...!!Shit!!!!
但是你的小雞吧看起來并不是這樣....它似乎很開心呢.....
But it sure looks like your dick....Is quite happy about all this....
我第一次看到你就從你身上感受到了那種感覺
The first time I saw you I can felt the feeling from you
那種我們彼此都深深感悟的感覺,那就是孤獨
A feeling like me. Is lonely
對對!就是要看你這副騷樣
Yes!Like this bitch face
表現的再淫蕩一點 你這母狗
So let's show them what a slut you are!
瞧瞧!2B!怎么了?你剛才那副很了不起的態度都跑哪里去了!
Come on!2B!What happened to the strongwilled girl i saw earlier!
都喝下去！咽下去！咽下去！咽下去！
Eat it all！Swallow it！Swallow it！Swallow it！
要是浪費一滴 就要你好看
Don't waste a drop,bitch!
來吸雞巴的背部
Suck it back
很好！讓你的小男友好好看看你那淫蕩的樣子
Yes, right！Let your boyfriend take a good look at your bitch face
接下來就把我的精子全部射到2B小姐的騷穴里吧.給我懷孕吧!!!
I'm gonna fill her with my baby juice and make 2B pregnant!!
我可要射了哦!給我懷孕吧!
Let's go!I'll impregnate you!
不要!別射里面!!!
No!!Don't cum inside!!
不要!饒了我吧!
No!!Stop it!
我感覺到有東西在里面流動.....
Pulsating inside me....
雞吧 還不拔出去么??
You're not going to take out your cock?
......2B
No！！！！2B
一個陌生男人的精液射進了我的子宮里......
A man I don't know is filling me with his semen.....
這就是我的第一次???
This is my frist time???
好過分...還當著那個少年的面
It's too cruel....In front of that boy's face
我的兄弟們都在等著呢
My brothers are waiting for their turn
好爽！
Pussy feels so good！
不要!饒了我吧!
No!!Stop it!
饒了我吧...
2B!!...
是夢嗎？？
A2???A dream???
我睡了多久？
How long have I slept?
你終于醒來了
Finally you woke up
2B！！2B她在哪里？？？
2B!!!Where's 2B？？？
她在哪？？？
Where's 2B？？？
她還在被肏 沒有時間休息
She doesn't have time to take a rest
什么？！
What??!!!
我將會把你帶出被殺與愛的死循環
You will get rid of the cycle from being killed and loved
只要你愿意 我們可以一起離開
You can walk out of the shadows with me whenever you like
什么？！
What??!!!
2B!!..
2B!!
不！！
No!!!
9S...
現在我只能我可奈何地被他們侵犯而已
Now I'm at my wits end. After being raped by them
你的臉怎么變成了這幅操行
You look like a bitch in heat
男人們一個接一個的侵犯我
One after another.Those guys kept fucking me
好妹子.就用我們的超速活塞必殺技把你肏到哭吧!
Good girl!!we'll make you cum with our high speed piston pumping!
他們往我的里面射入精液
They were soiling their semen into me
別忍著了.讓你的男朋友好好看著你這副被肏哭的臉
Don't be patient. Let your boyfriend look at your face
被我們輪奸之后就變成白癡一樣了
All this rape has turned her into an idiot
這樣就能懷上我的孩子了吧??
Now you'll have my baby for sure!
你他媽的又溢出來了
Did you wet yourself again??
這個小騷屄.這是第幾發了!?
You bitch!!How many times has it been!?
嘿!看啊!她又被肏暈過去了
Hey!look!She fainted again
但是2B的小騷穴還挺精神的呢!
But 2B's pussy is still lively
讓我們繼續肏她把!
We should fuck her even more!
2B小姐 你可沒有時間給我在這里休息啊
Miss 2B you don't have time to rest
這些人可都等著用大雞巴插你呢
All these guys are going to fuck you now
所有人勃起的大雞巴都在等著插你
Everyone's throbbing cocks are waiting for you
好戲開場了
It's showtime
所有的....人么???
All......of them???
Plunge it in!!!Put it in!!!
插進去! 插進去!插進去! 插進去!
是的 整個軍隊 都是你的老朋友哦
Yes the all the army of your old friends
你要被所有人肏到翻
All of them will have sex with you!
不要！
No!
不要...
No!!...
與其接受這種恥辱..請殺了我!!!
I'm not going to take this humiliation....plz kill me....!!
現在我沒法面對9S了
Now I can not face 9S
究竟已經被這幫家伙侵犯了多久了....???
How long are they planning to rape me....???
太粗暴了....
Too.....rough
這個喉嚨真棒啊
This throat pussy is the best
連反抗的力氣也失去了我開始停止思考.....
I lost my will to fight and stopped thinkings about it....
哦.2B小姐姐.你可真沉啊
Oh.2B sister You're so heavy
開始因為作為女人而被侵犯感到喜悅
Soon I even started to enjoy it
快點啊 2B小姐姐!
Let's hurry up a little 2B!
我們的士兵可不喜歡干等著!
Our soldiers don't like to wait!
她的奶子也很色呢
Her boobs are gorgeous
這么快????
That's too fast!!
不要 不要啊!!!
NO!!!No!!!
對不起...9S...
9S..I'm..sorry....
我們再也不能一起回到過去了
We are never ever getting back together
壞結局-埃米爾的移動商店
圍困已經消失，但戰爭還遠未結束
The siege is lost, but the war is far from over
轉眼之間，一切都結束了
It was all over in the blink of an eye
慰安婦
我們成了埃米爾商店的商品
We became a commodity in the Emil store
安いよ～
超便宜喲~
我不知道埃米爾的意圖，但他似乎在收集某種東西
I don't know Emil's purpose but  he seems to be collecting something
アイテムが安いんだ
商品賣得超級便宜
買おう～
快來買哦~
お値打ち品あります
本店出售實惠商品
安いよ～
超便宜喲~
道具とか安いんだ
道具價格也超便宜
やばいよ～
不得了咯~
値引きはも
還想要砍價？
無～理～！
沒~門兒~！
為何孩子們的內心充滿了憎恨
Who taught these children how to hate
孩子們...
my children!
為何你們會變成這樣？
How did these kids turn into this?
埃米爾，你對孩子們都做了什么？
Emil what did you do to the children?
いらっしゃい～
歡迎光臨~
まいどあり～
下次再來~
毎日安売りだ
本店天天都打折
いらっしゃい～
歡迎光臨~
まいどあり～
下次再來~
出血大奉仕～
出血大甩賣~
いらっしゃい～
歡迎光臨~
まいどあり～
下次再來~
商んとかどっこいしょ
超特價 嘿了個咻
いらっしゃい～
歡迎光臨~
まいどあり～
下次再來~
今日も楽しい日だな！
今天也是開心的一天！
求求你們放過我吧！
Plea....se..stop！
放過我吧..
Stop!!...
你們不能對2B小姐和A2小姐這么做
You can't do this to Miss 2B and A2. It's impossible
我想這里有人在搗鬼 你們都被利用了
I think somebody's pulled a fast one here. You are being used
恐怕會有不好的事情發生
Afraid that something bad will happen
不要啊！
No...no!!!
拔出去啊！
Get it off me!
饒了我吧...
No...stop!!!
放過我吧...
No...Please!!!
求求你們..不要啊啊啊啊！！
Please...Nooooooooooo!!!
不要射進來啊！
No! Don't cum inside！
最后埃米爾成功地完成了他的實驗
Finally Emil succeeded in his experiment
他喚醒了死去的妹妹
His dead sister was summoned
來自地獄的怪物現在出現在我們面前
This monster from hell Now appear in front of us
我無法思考接下來會發生什么
I can't think what will happen
不要啊!放開我 畜生!!!
No!!Let go of me, you vicious monster!
不要！
No！
我從沒見過這么大的陰莖
I've never seen such a huge penis
你想要什么都行！唯獨這個是不行的！
Tell me what you want!This is impossible!
求你了 放我下來...
Put me down,I beg you
這場面太可怕了！
The scene was too terrible!
我驚訝得簡直不敢相信自己的眼睛
I was so astonished that I could hardly believe my eyes
不要！
No!!!
不要啊！你要做什么？
No!!!What are you doing?
不要啊！
No...no!!!
你要做...
What are you...
放過我吧...
No...Please!!!
命運就像被強奸 你無法抗拒 必須學會享受。
Fate is like rape, you can not resist must learn to enjoy
好結局-純愛
9S！！
2B！！
9...S...
9S...
2B！！
謝謝觀賞